cioreview.com 2018-12-26

# CIOReview : Privacy Policy

This website collects personally identifying information and data about individuals, their company, and their company's demographics (personally identifying information and data) including (i) when you provide information to us, such as when you register or sign up for any of our products such as subscriptions, e-mails, newsletters, memberships, RSS Feeds, White Papers, conferences and other communications with the Publisher, (ii) when you register for any other CIOReview products individually, your information will be known to the publisher and (iii) from time to time we may add other information that we collect from third party sources to enhance the information that you provided to the Publisher.

Below is the current policy regarding the usage of personally identifying information and data collected by the Publisher. We re-evaluate this policy on an ongoing basis based on feedback from readers. The Publisher reserves the right to change its privacy policy. However, if there are any changes to the use of personally identifying information and data that is different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Website.

The Publisher or one of our affiliated websites, or third party partners or advertisers may place online tracking technology such as a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, except when such information has been supplied by a subscriber or registered user. In addition, cookies placed in the browser files of a user's computer by a third party advertiser, may be used by the advertiser to collect web viewing data to serve further online interest-based advertising, also known as online behavioral advertising..

However, we cannot link that user ID acquired by the “cookie” with personally identifying information and data about you such as your name or e-mail address.

Other cookies without personally identifying information and data are used to enable the Publisher to manage the banner advertisements presented or personalized information to the user.

Browsers or third-party software can allow you to block the use of cookies while you surf our site. Or, you can use third-party "anonymizer" services to mask information in your cookies, or even general data such as your IP address. In such cases you would not be able to take advantage of most of the personalization services offered by the Publisher site(s).

The aggregated information we collect is used for a number of purposes including the following:  
1\. to improve the content and design of our website.  
2\. to help advertisers, potential advertisers or marketers assess the suitability of our Website for their ad campaigns.  
3\. as clear GIFs, also known as pixel tags, provided by our ad-serving company to help manage online advertising. These clear GIFS let our ad-serving company recognize a browser's cookie when a user visits our site. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable (It does not include your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address).  
4\. We may create and use aggregate customer data to understand more about the interests of our customers and may use the data to offer goods and services we believe may be of interest to our customers, on behalf of the Publisher or select organizations.

Mobile, Telephone numbers, Postal addresses, and other personally identifying information and data may be collected from our online users (and, as applicable, our print subscribers) and may be used to promote the Publisher’s products and services, and may be rented and/or licensed to select outside firms for promotional purposes. Offers for which the personally identifying information and data are rented and/or licensed for use and the users are required to target their offers carefully. With your express consent, your mobile telephone number may be used to promote other products and services of the Publisher, as well as the products and services of other related companies. Further, your mobile phone number may, with your express consent, be used to promote the products and services of carefully chosen third parties. At any time you may "opt-out" of receiving communications via your mobile phone from the Publisher and other third parties, by writing to the address provided in the “Contact Us” section or by clicking the unsubscribe link of any individual message you may receive. Because many phone companies recycle phone numbers, it is possible for users who purchase a new phone to receive messages that the previous owner had subscribed to or otherwise consented to receive.

Email addresses and Fax numbers may be collected from our online users (and, as applicable, our print subscribers) and may be used by the Publisher to collect re-qualification data, and may be used for surveys for the Publisher and third parties. Except as set forth in this policy no fax numbers are rented and/or licensed to outside firms.

Users who later decide they want to change any of their preferences may do so at [www.cioreview.com/newsletter/](https://www.cioreview.com/newsletter/)

(Online users who are also print subscribers should refer to the print subscriber section of this policy which contains information on how to remove your name from our promotion list).

Our Website makes available a large library of content provided to us from third parties. When accessing content contributed by a third party, your personally identifying information may be shared with those third parties, and the information will be governed by those parties' privacy policies as well as ours. The Publisher, nor the parent company, or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates, do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of such third parties. If you do not wish to have your information shared with a third party, please do not access third party content on our site.

Our Website, or portions of our Website, may be sponsored by third party sponsors. Any personally identifying information you share on our Website when registering to receive access to any offer, including but not limited to newsletter content, may be shared with such sponsors for marketing purposes.

Our Website users should be aware that when they disclose personally identifying information (e.g., address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and E-mail address) in areas that are publicly accessible by others, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties. Neither the Publisher, nor its parent company or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates are responsible for any information that you provide in the above areas.

In the event that the ownership of this Website and/or any of the Publisher's other products and/or assets are sold or transferred, all lists and data which contain personally identifying information and data including for example address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and e-mail address, will be transferred to the new owner.

We may use or disclose personally identifying information if we have a good-faith belief that the disclosure is reasonably necessary (a) to satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) to enforce agreements we have with you, (c) to address fraud or security issues, or (d) to protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of the Publisher, or our employees or customers.

**Important Notice**  
This private assertion and its enumerated regulations are supposed to conform with regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 ("GDPR") and provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your personal facts in accordance with the GDPR.

**Privacy of Children**  
This Children's Online Privacy Policy explains our information collection, disclosure, and parental consent practices with respect to information provided by children under the age of 13 ("child" or "children"), such as name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect (nor do we wish to collect) any personally identifiable information or other user information from children under the age of 13. The Sites are controlled and operated by us from the United States and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. We support the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), and our goal is to minimize the information gathered from and disseminated about kids under 13 while permitting them active participation in the trustworthy information, education and independent voice for which we are known.

**Print Subscriber Privacy Policy**  
The Publisher collects personally identifying information and data about individuals their company and the company's demographics (personally identifying information and data) (i) when you provide information to us, such as when you register or sign up for any of our products such as subscriptions, RSS Feeds, White Papers, emails, newsletters, memberships and other communications with the Publisher (ii) when you subscribe to one or our websites or products, your information will be known to the Publisher and (iii) from time to time we may add other information that we collect from third party sources to enhance the information that you provided to the Publisher.

Below is the current policy regarding the usage of personally identifying information and data collected by the Publisher. We re-evaluate this policy on an ongoing basis based on feedback from readers. The Publisher reserves the right to change its privacy policy. However, if there are any changes to the use of personally identifying information and data that is different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you by posting a notice on our Website.

Subscribers for the Publisher's Print subscriptions are asked to complete a questionnaire with personally identifying information and demographics. The data is used in a number of ways including the following:  
1\. to improve the content of the Publisher's print product(s)  
2\. to notify subscribers about re-qualification and renewal  
3\. used by us for marketing the Publisher's products and services  
4\. used by the Publisher, its subsidiaries for research surveys  
5\. used by Publisher for consultation with readers

In the event that the ownership of the Publisher's print product or any of the Publisher's other products and/or assets are sold, the lists and data which contain personally identifying information and data including for example address, company name, telephone number, demographic information, buying information, other data and e-mail address, will be transferred to the new owner.

We may use or disclose personally identifying information if we have a good-faith belief that the disclosure is reasonably necessary (a) to satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) to enforce agreements we have with you, (c) to address fraud or security issues, or (d) to protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of the Publisher, or our employees or customers.
